<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-02-24T00:27:27+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Remi De Coster</title><subtitle>Electrical Engineer
</subtitle><author><name>Remi De Coster</name></author><entry><title type="html">Low-Cost Tethered Drone</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/low-cost-tethered-drone.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Low-Cost Tethered Drone" /><published>2025-01-31T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-01-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/low-cost-tethered-drone</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/low-cost-tethered-drone.html">&lt;p&gt;Tethered drones are a good solution for applications requiring long-duration flight, consistent power delivery, and secure communication. Unlike traditional drones that rely on onboard batteries, tethered drones are connected to a ground station via a physical tether, enabling &lt;strong&gt;continuous operation while maintaining a secure and interference-resistant data link&lt;/strong&gt;. These systems are increasingly popular in security and surveillance applications, offering real-time aerial monitoring without the risk of signal interception or limited flight time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/pcb/pcb-acdc-700W.png&quot; alt=&quot;kart&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a recent project, I explored &lt;strong&gt;low-cost solutions&lt;/strong&gt; for tethered drones by looking into different electrical architectures. The goal was to determine the feasibility of drone systems that provide reliable power and communication while maintaining affordability and scalability for diverse use cases. In particular we compared both &lt;strong&gt;AC tether&lt;/strong&gt; systems and &lt;strong&gt;high voltage DC tether&lt;/strong&gt; systems, in both centralized and distributed power topologies. Communication signals were transmitted over the same lines used to deliver power, utilizing &lt;strong&gt;signal superposition&lt;/strong&gt; to combine both functionalities within a single tether.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Remi De Coster</name></author><category term="project" /><category term="drones" /><category term="power" /><summary type="html">Tethered drones are a good solution for applications requiring long-duration flight, consistent power delivery, and secure communication. Unlike traditional drones that rely on onboard batteries, tethered drones are connected to a ground station via a physical tether, enabling continuous operation while maintaining a secure and interference-resistant data link. These systems are increasingly popular in security and surveillance applications, offering real-time aerial monitoring without the risk of signal interception or limited flight time.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Diagnostic Tool For Farming Vehicles</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/diagnostic-tool-for-farming-vehicles.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Diagnostic Tool For Farming Vehicles" /><published>2024-11-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2024-11-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/diagnostic-tool-for-farming-vehicles</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/diagnostic-tool-for-farming-vehicles.html">&lt;p&gt;Agricultural vehicles often face wire harness issues due to the harsh environments in which they operate. Factors such as water ingress, punctures, ruptures, or structural damage to cables can significantly impact their performance. During the design phase, vehicle engineers struggle to &lt;strong&gt;identify potential failure points or weak spots in the wire harness&lt;/strong&gt;. For maintenance technicians, locating broken wire segments or loose connections is a time-consuming task, often necessitating the replacement of the entire harness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/tdr-tractor/harvester.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Harvester&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/tdr-tractor/harvester2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Harvester&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To address this challenge, I developed hardware that periodically performs &lt;strong&gt;time-domain reflectometry (TDR)&lt;/strong&gt; measurements on multiple signal lines within the wire harness. TDR enables vehicle owners to visualize the impedance of the wires, making it possible to detect performance issues at specific locations. The hardware is installed between the vehicle’s main computer and the wire harness and is capable of isolating individual signal lines for measurement. The system automatically runs diagnostics during the vehicle’s startup and shutdown processes. Multiplexers are employed to switch between signal lines, directing them to the TDR measurement device. Measurements are stored in the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Remi De Coster</name></author><category term="example" /><summary type="html">Agricultural vehicles often face wire harness issues due to the harsh environments in which they operate. Factors such as water ingress, punctures, ruptures, or structural damage to cables can significantly impact their performance. During the design phase, vehicle engineers struggle to identify potential failure points or weak spots in the wire harness. For maintenance technicians, locating broken wire segments or loose connections is a time-consuming task, often necessitating the replacement of the entire harness.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kart With Hybrid Energy Storage System</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/kart-with-hybrid-energy-storage-system.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kart With Hybrid Energy Storage System" /><published>2024-10-22T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2024-10-22T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/kart-with-hybrid-energy-storage-system</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/kart-with-hybrid-energy-storage-system.html">&lt;p&gt;By combining energy storage technologies with complementary features, we achieved a significantly extended driving range without sacrificing acceleration performance in a small electric vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;semi-solid-state battery&lt;/strong&gt; uses a semi-solid electrolyte, offering higher energy density and improved safety compared to conventional batteries. The kart packs 6 kWh of energy in a compartment the size of a backpack, achieving an impressive energy density of 750 Wh/L or 350 Wh/kg. For this module I had to connect and configure a BMS system that would fit in the limited space available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;supercapacitor&lt;/strong&gt; module I developed has an energy capacity comparable to that of a smartphone, but can charge and discharge at a massive 24 kilowatts of continuous power. This fast power delivery is ideal for rapid acceleration. This module was completely custom designed and manufactured by me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/hybrid-kart/kart2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;kart&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/hybrid-kart/kart1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;kart&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I created the electric and control architectures, and led both the hardware and software implementation. The main controller uses CAN to receive status information from both modules and uses an on-board network server to publish live data over UDP. A dashboard user interface with speed dial and vehicle information was created using Flask.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Remi De Coster</name></author><category term="project" /><summary type="html">By combining energy storage technologies with complementary features, we achieved a significantly extended driving range without sacrificing acceleration performance in a small electric vehicle. A semi-solid-state battery uses a semi-solid electrolyte, offering higher energy density and improved safety compared to conventional batteries. The kart packs 6 kWh of energy in a compartment the size of a backpack, achieving an impressive energy density of 750 Wh/L or 350 Wh/kg. For this module I had to connect and configure a BMS system that would fit in the limited space available. The supercapacitor module I developed has an energy capacity comparable to that of a smartphone, but can charge and discharge at a massive 24 kilowatts of continuous power. This fast power delivery is ideal for rapid acceleration. This module was completely custom designed and manufactured by me.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Webtool For Battery Sizing</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/webtool-for-battery-sizing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Webtool For Battery Sizing" /><published>2024-09-01T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2024-09-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/webtool-for-battery-sizing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/webtool-for-battery-sizing.html">&lt;p&gt;Hybrid Battery Energy Storage Systems (HBESS) combine two distinct but complementary cell technologies in a single battery solution. For example, a battery cell technology with a high energy density like NMC could be combined with a battery cell technology with high power density like LTO. In this way, a sort of ‘composite’ battery storage can be created which has the benefits of both cell technologies used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/sizing-tool/sizing-tool2.png&quot; alt=&quot;kart&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/sizing-tool/sizing-tool1.png&quot; alt=&quot;kart&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More difficult becomes the sizing and control of such hybrid battery systems. At what times will you use the “High Energy” cells, and at what times do you use the “High Power”. Using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.casadi.org/&quot;&gt;CasADi&lt;/a&gt; framework non-linear optimization within Python, I created a web tool which can be used to design an optimal hybrid battery system, minimizing either the total cost, volume or weight. The webtool is created using the Streamlit framework, and is hosted using Azure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tool makes clear what theoritical benefits hybrid battery solutions can bring for demanding applications like maritime, construction and transportation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The tool is available on &lt;a href=&quot;http://battery.flandersmake.be&quot;&gt;battery.flandersmake.be&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name>Remi De Coster</name></author><category term="test" /><summary type="html">Hybrid Battery Energy Storage Systems (HBESS) combine two distinct but complementary cell technologies in a single battery solution. For example, a battery cell technology with a high energy density like NMC could be combined with a battery cell technology with high power density like LTO. In this way, a sort of ‘composite’ battery storage can be created which has the benefits of both cell technologies used.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Drone Docking Station</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/drone-docking-station.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Drone Docking Station" /><published>2024-07-19T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2024-07-19T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/drone-docking-station</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/drone-docking-station.html">&lt;p&gt;Content coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/docking-station/docking-station1.gif&quot; alt=&quot;docking-station&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Remi De Coster</name></author><category term="test" /><summary type="html">Content coming soon!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Power Station For Greenhouse</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/power-station-for-greenhouse.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Power Station For Greenhouse" /><published>2024-04-09T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2024-04-09T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/power-station-for-greenhouse</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/power-station-for-greenhouse.html">&lt;p&gt;Autonomous drones hold significant potential in agricultural applications, such as flower counting, yield estimation, scarecrow functionality, and disease detection. To effectively leverage this technology, it is essential to have a reliable infrastructure for real-time data monitoring and communication. For research purposes, we have a greenhouse setup where new algorithms, hardware, and software can be tested and refined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/greenhouse/greenhouse2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;greenhouse&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/greenhouse/greenhouse3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;greenhouse&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/greenhouse/greenhouse1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;greenhouse&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To support these operations, I designed a power system that ensures constant availability of both internet connectivity and 230VAC power within the greenhouse. This system utilizes a 4G router for seamless internet access and a solar panel to sustainably provide energy, ensuring the greenhouse remains operational without relying on an external power grid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The system also integrates a single-board computer housed in the electrical cabinet, which hosts a Flask web page to monitor the greenhouse’s status. Key environmental parameters, such as temperature, humidity, and live camera feeds, are continuously updated and accessible remotely. This allows for real-time monitoring and analysis, facilitating the development and testing of autonomous drone applications in agricultural settings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/greenhouse/greenhouse4.png&quot; alt=&quot;greenhouse&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content><author><name>Remi De Coster</name></author><category term="test" /><summary type="html">Autonomous drones hold significant potential in agricultural applications, such as flower counting, yield estimation, scarecrow functionality, and disease detection. To effectively leverage this technology, it is essential to have a reliable infrastructure for real-time data monitoring and communication. For research purposes, we have a greenhouse setup where new algorithms, hardware, and software can be tested and refined.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hackathon Battlefield Of Iot</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hackathon-battlefield-of-iot.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hackathon Battlefield Of Iot" /><published>2024-03-01T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2024-03-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hackathon-battlefield-of-iot</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hackathon-battlefield-of-iot.html">&lt;p&gt;Content coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Had an incredible time participating in the Battlefield of Things IoT hashtag#hackathon hosted by Belgian Defence over the weekend. Tasked with the challenge of surveilling a large area using low-power, secure and easily deployable devices, we set off to develop a solution within 48 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team rose to the challenge by engineering an encrypted mesh network of sensor nodes utilizing hashtag#LoRa radio modules for long range transmission over multiple kilometers, facilitated by ESP32 microcontrollers. Each node was armed with a GPS module and a suite of sensors, empowering us to detect and localize human presence at a very low cost. 📡🗺&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/hackathon/hackathon1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;hackathon&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/hackathon/hackathon2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;hackathon&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Remi De Coster</name></author><category term="test" /><summary type="html">Content coming soon!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Disease Detection In Fruit Orchards</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/disease-detection-in-fruit-orchards.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Disease Detection In Fruit Orchards" /><published>2023-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/disease-detection-in-fruit-orchards</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/disease-detection-in-fruit-orchards.html">&lt;p&gt;Content coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/projects/fruit-orchards/fruit-orchards1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Harvester&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Remi De Coster</name></author><category term="example" /><summary type="html">Content coming soon!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Resonant Switching Dcdc Converter</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/resonant-switching-dcdc-converter.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Resonant Switching Dcdc Converter" /><published>2022-06-01T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2022-06-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/resonant-switching-dcdc-converter</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/resonant-switching-dcdc-converter.html">&lt;p&gt;My master thesis covered the topic of the design and validation of a resonant switching LLC DC/DC converter for the auxilariy systems of a solar car. These low-power (&amp;lt;25W) auxilary systems include the vehicle dashboard, communication modules, brake lights, horn, blinkers… The converter has to work for a wide range (difference of 80V) of input voltages due to the battery system connected to the input.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/pcb/pcb-llc-half-bridge.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;pcb&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both half-bridge and full-bridge rectification variants were created. The ICE2HS01G IC by Infineon was used. The final esults were underwhelming, the LLC converter was not deemed suitable for a low power application due to its complexity and large BOM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/pcb/pcb-llc-full-bridge.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;pcb&quot; class=&quot;ioda&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content><author><name>Remi De Coster</name></author><category term="test" /><summary type="html">My master thesis covered the topic of the design and validation of a resonant switching LLC DC/DC converter for the auxilariy systems of a solar car. These low-power (&amp;lt;25W) auxilary systems include the vehicle dashboard, communication modules, brake lights, horn, blinkers… The converter has to work for a wide range (difference of 80V) of input voltages due to the battery system connected to the input.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Post Example With Headings And Toc</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/post-example-with-headings-and-toc.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Post Example With Headings And Toc" /><published>2020-07-09T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-07-09T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/post-example-with-headings-and-toc</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/post-example-with-headings-and-toc.html">&lt;p&gt;Mauris viverra dictum ultricies. Vestibulum quis ipsum euismod, facilisis metus sed, varius ipsum. Donec scelerisque lacus libero, eu dignissim sem venenatis at. Nunc a egestas tortor, sed feugiat leo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;table-of-contents&quot;&gt;Table of contents&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#table-of-contents&quot;&gt;Table of contents&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#the-start&quot;&gt;The start&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#the-middle&quot;&gt;The middle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#the-end&quot;&gt;The end&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mauris viverra dictum ultricies. Vestibulum quis ipsum euismod, facilisis metus sed, varius ipsum. Donec scelerisque lacus libero, eu dignissim sem venenatis at. Nunc a egestas tortor, sed feugiat leo. Vestibulum porta tincidunt tellus, vitae ornare tortor. Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Sed nunc neque, tempor in iaculis non, faucibus et metus. Etiam id nisl ut lorem gravida euismod.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-start&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#the-start&quot;&gt;The start&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fusce non velit cursus ligula mattis convallis vel at metus. Sed pharetra tellus massa, non elementum eros vulputate non. Suspendisse potenti. Quisque arcu felis, laoreet vel accumsan sit amet, fermentum at nunc. Sed massa quam, auctor in eros quis, porttitor tincidunt orci. Nulla convallis id sapien ornare viverra. Cras nec est lacinia ligula porta tincidunt. Nam a est eget ligula pellentesque posuere. Maecenas quis enim ac risus accumsan scelerisque. Aliquam vitae libero sapien. Etiam convallis, metus nec suscipit condimentum, quam massa congue velit, sit amet sollicitudin nisi tortor a lectus. Cras a arcu enim. Suspendisse hendrerit euismod est ac gravida. Donec vitae elit tristique, suscipit eros at, aliquam augue. In ac faucibus dui. Sed tempor lacus tristique elit sagittis, vitae tempor massa convallis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-middle&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#the-middle&quot;&gt;The middle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proin quis velit et eros auctor laoreet. Aenean eget nibh odio. Suspendisse mollis enim pretium, fermentum urna vitae, egestas purus. Donec convallis tincidunt purus, scelerisque fermentum eros sagittis vel. Aliquam ac aliquet risus, tempus iaculis est. Fusce molestie mauris non interdum hendrerit. Curabitur ullamcorper, eros vitae interdum volutpat, lacus magna lacinia turpis, at accumsan dui tortor vel lectus. Aenean risus massa, semper non lectus rutrum, facilisis imperdiet mi. Praesent sed quam quis purus auctor ornare et sed augue. Vestibulum non quam quis ligula luctus placerat sed sit amet erat. Vestibulum ante ipsum primis in faucibus orci luctus et ultrices posuere cubilia curae; Fusce auctor, sem eu volutpat dignissim, turpis nibh malesuada arcu, in consequat elit mauris quis sem. Nam tristique sit amet enim vel accumsan. Sed id nibh commodo, dictum sem id, semper quam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-end&quot;&gt;The end&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donec ex lectus, tempus non lacinia quis, pretium non ipsum. Praesent est nunc, rutrum vel tellus eu, tristique laoreet purus. In rutrum orci sit amet ex ornare, sit amet finibus lacus laoreet. Etiam ac facilisis purus, eget porttitor odio. Suspendisse tempus dolor nec risus sodales posuere. Proin dui dui, mollis a consectetur molestie, lobortis vitae tellus. Vivamus at purus sed urna sollicitudin mattis. Mauris lacinia libero in lobortis pulvinar. Nullam sit amet condimentum justo. Donec orci justo, pharetra ut dolor non, interdum finibus orci. Proin vitae ante a dui sodales commodo ac id elit. Nunc vel accumsan nunc, sit amet congue nunc. Aliquam in lacinia velit. Integer lobortis luctus eros, in fermentum metus aliquet a. Class aptent taciti sociosqu ad litora torquent per conubia nostra, per inceptos himenaeos.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Remi De Coster</name></author><category term="example2" /><summary type="html">Mauris viverra dictum ultricies. Vestibulum quis ipsum euismod, facilisis metus sed, varius ipsum. Donec scelerisque lacus libero, eu dignissim sem venenatis at. Nunc a egestas tortor, sed feugiat leo.</summary></entry></feed>